// objects of questions (10) with answers, the correct answer, and explanation
// The correct answer property will have the idx # for single answer questions
// And for Correct (Yes) / Incorrect (No) questions, true = 'Correct', false = 'Incorrect'


const spellingQuiz = [
  {
    question: 'Cappuccino',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Correct',
    explanation: null
  },

  {
    question: 'Arabicia',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Incorrect',
    explanation: 'It\'s Arabica'
  },

  {
    question: 'Macchiato',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Correct',
    explanation: null
  },

  {
    question: 'Frappacinno',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Incorrect',
    explanation: 'It\'s Frappuccino'
  },

  {
    question: 'Espresso',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Correct',
    explanation: null
  },

  {
    question: 'Ristretto',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Correct',
    explanation: null
  },

  {
    question: 'Caffiene',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Incorrect',
    explanation: 'It\'s Caffeine'
  },

  {
    question: 'Caffé au Laite',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Incorrect',
    explanation: 'It\'s Caffé au Lait'
  },

  {
    question: 'Robusta',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Correct',
    explanation: null
  },

  {
    question: 'Kopi Lawak',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Incorrect',
    explanation: 'It\'s Kopi Luwak'
  },
];

const loverQuiz = [
  {
    question: 'Kopi Lawak',
    options: ['Incorrect', 'Correct'],
    answer: 'Incorrect',
    explanation: 'It\'s Kopi Luwak'
  },
]